<LanguageData>

	<NB_DefleXitol.label>DefleXitol</NB_DefleXitol.label>
	<NB_DefleXitol.description>DefleXitol is a military stimulator designed for front line fighters. It slightly increases survivability, allowing you to survive a couple of extra hits.</NB_DefleXitol.description>

	<NB_PyroForm.label>PyroForm</NB_PyroForm.label>
	<NB_PyroForm.description>Pyroform is heavily used by various military defense companies when their opponent is a tribe of imps, or some other bunch of pyromaniacs. Highly valued among hemophages.</NB_PyroForm.description>

	<NB_MulE.label>Mul-E</NB_MulE.label>
	<NB_MulE.description>Many traders use Mul-E both on their own and to improve the carrying capacity of their animals. This is useful when traveling long distances, but keep in mind that while Mul-E is active, you are vulnerable.</NB_MulE.description>

	<NB_Trasylol_500k.label>Trasylol 500k</NB_Trasylol_500k.label>
	<NB_Trasylol_500k.description>Trasylol has the number 500k in its name for a reason. 500,000 is the number of units produced before they were banned en masse. Whether it was the effectiveness, corruption, or side effects, no one knows anymore.</NB_Trasylol_500k.description>

	<NB_Regenostas.label>Regenosts</NB_Regenostas.label>
	<NB_Regenostas.description>Regenostasis can heal all physical wounds in the shortest possible time. It cannot heal your mental wounds, no matter how much you inject it.</NB_Regenostas.description>

	<NB_Dofa.label>Dofa</NB_Dofa.label>
	<NB_Dofa.description>Ask any native of the advanced world what drug they have the most demanded - you will hear Dofa. And it is not without reason - Dofa is useful for everyone: a scientist, a builder, a cook, even a miner or a kindergartener! \n\nHas contraindications, consult a doctor before use.</NB_Dofa.description>

	<NB_Flexitol.label>Flexitol</NB_Flexitol.label>
	<NB_Flexitol.description>Party? Flexitol! Studying? Flexitol! Flexitol is useful for everyone, you can't imagine your future life without it. You want Flexitol, you love Flexitol, you're ready to take it day in and day out. It may even have too much of a narcotic effect.</NB_Flexitol.description>

</LanguageData>